不是他不想跟你说
是你根本就没有给他机会
我当时确实生气
可那也是因为有误会
所以才对他发了脾气
他之后为什么不说
陆总你要不要好好想一想
那天之后发生了什么事情
需要我帮你好好回忆一下
在这个项目上我耗费了多少心血
可是你能拿他怎么办呢
毕竟他还是你的太太
早知道今天我早就应该跟他离婚
苍宇
这是你的真心话吗
真的想跟我离婚吗
我这辈子做过最后悔的事情
就是跟你结婚
你也跟外面那些人一样
觉得我是一头又丑又肥的猪
对吗
你也知道外面那些人怎么说你
你的确又丑又肥
但我说我可以容忍你找人相助
我接受不了你脑子也是一头猪
我知道了
所以那天他出车祸
是因为我骂了他
It's not that he doesn't want to tell you.
You didn't give him a chance at all
I was angry.
But that's also because of a misunderstanding.
So I got angry with him
Why didn't he say anything after that?
Mr. Lu, do you want to think about it?
What happened after that day?
Need me to help you remember
How much effort did I put into this project?
But what can you do with him?
After all, he is still your wife
I should have divorced him a long time ago today
Cangyu
Is that true?
Do you really want to divorce me?
The thing I regret the most in my life
Is to marry you
You are just like those people out there
Think I'm an ugly and fat pig
Right?
You know what those people outside say about you
You are ugly and fat
But I said I could tolerate you looking for help
I can't accept that your brain is also a pig.
Oh, I see.
So he got in a car accident that day.
It's because I scolded him